<resources>
    <string name="Fitness_Care">Fitness_care</string>
    <string name="s">Snap Scren</string>
    <string name="imageview" />
    <string name="my_workout">My Workout</string>
    <string name="diet_plans">Diet Plans</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="reminders">Reminders</string>
    <string name="exercises_yoga_etc">Exercises(Yoga etc..)</string>
    <string name="textview">textview</string>
    <string name="title_activity_yoga_exe">yoga_exe</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="yoga_text">\nYoga is an ancient physical\n
         and spiritual discipline and
         branch of philosophy that
         originated in India reportedly
         more than 5,000 years ago.
         The word yoga comes from
         the Sanskrit word yuj, which
         means to yoke, join, or unite.\n\n\t
        Yoga is an old discipline from India. It is both spiritual and physical.
        Yoga uses breathing techniques, exercise and meditation.
        It helps to improve health and happiness.\n \t\t Yoga is a systematic practice of physical
        exercise, breath control, relaxation, diet control, and positive thinking
        and meditation aimed at developing harmony in the body, mind, and environment.\n"</string>
            <string name="cardio_text">

                 Cardio exercise is any exercise that
                raises your heart rate. Face it our bodies
                were made to move.And we all know that to
                keep our muscles in shape we need move them.
                This movement makes them stronger
                and stronger muscles make for a more efficient
                and healthy body. \n\n \t Your heart is a muscle.
                Therefore working it makes it stronger.
                A stronger cardio-vascular system means more
                capillaries delivering more oxygen to cells in your muscles.
                This enables your cells to burn more fat during both exercise and inactivity.
               \n\n\t Cardio exercise uses large muscle movement over
                a sustained period of time keeping your heart rate
                to at least 50% of its maximum level.</string>

    <string name="zumba_text">
        Zumba is a popular fitness program inspired by Latin dance.
        The word "Zumba" comes from a Colombian word that means
        to move fast and have fun, which is just how people describe
        the routine. Using upbeat Latin music
        together with cardiovascular exercise, Zumba is aerobic dancing that
        is lots of fun and easy to learn. \n\n \t Zumba seems to be an optimal fitness choice,
        mixing cardio intervals with resistance training. Many experts believe that an interval/resistance
        combination maximizes caloric output, fat burning, and total body toning. Zumba mixes effective body
        sculpting movements with easy-to-follow, fun dance steps. People seem to forget about working
        out during a Zumba session, allowing them to exercise longer, and burn even more calories.
        \n\n\t A typical Zumba session lasts about an hour and incorporates several dance styles, including cumbia,
        merengue, salsa, reggaeton, mambo, rumba, flamenco, and calypso and Salsaton. The Latin music
        includes both fast and slow rhythms, allowing for a great cardio workout as well as body sculpting exercises.
        Depending on the instructor, you may even get a taste of belly dancing or hip-hop dancing, too.</string>

</resources>
